showcasecinemas.co.uk 2018-02-02

# Terms & Conditions| SHOWCASE

Privacy Policy for use of NATL. Amusements (UK) Limited Web sites

NATL. Amusements (UK) Limited is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. This Privacy Policy explains how we use the information we collect about you and procedures we have in place to safeguard your privacy.

In this Privacy Policy references to we, us and our are to NATL. Amusements (UK) Limited. References to the Website are to www.showcasecinemas.co.uk and www.cinemadelux.co.uk.

What Information we Collect

The information we collect via the Website may include:

Personal details you give us through completion of forms on the Website, including name, address, telephone number, email address etc.  
Debit or credit card information which we need to pass to a bank or card processing agency for verification.  
Your IP address, your preferences and use of email updates.  
Data recorded by the Website which allows us to recognise you and your preferred settings. Such data is recorded locally on your computer through the use of cookies. Your browser can be programmed to reject cookies or warn you before downloading them.

What we do with your Information

Any personal information we collect from the Website we use for some or all of the following purposes:

To process your registration and your orders for products and services.  
In some cases we may use your email address to send you information on other products and services. You will be offered the option to opt in or out of such service.  
We may need to pass the information we collect to other companies for administrative purposes. We may use third parties to carry out certain activities such as processing and sorting data, monitoring use of the Website etc. Such third parties will not be allowed to use your personal information for their own purposes.  
We may also provide your information to carefully selected third parties whose products or services we believe may be of interest to you. In such case, you will be offered the option to opt out of such service.  
We may use aggregated information for the purpose of monitoring use of the Website. Such aggregated information may be provided to third parties. These statistics will not include information which can be used to identify any individual.

How we protect your Information

The internet is not a secure medium. However, we have put in place recommended up to date security measures and will review these and keep them updated regularly.  
Subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy, we keep your information confidential. For details of procedures in relation to subject access and disclosure of your information please contact [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection), marking your email for the attention of the Data Controller at NATL. Amusements (UK) Limited.

Updating your Details

If any of the details you have provided the Website changes, please give us correct details by email to [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#790c121a0a3917180d10161718155418140c0a1c141c170d0a571a1614 "Customer Services")

Your Consent

By submitting your information on the Website, you consent to the use of that information as set out in this Privacy Policy. If we change the Privacy Policy we will post the changes on this page and we may place notices on other pages of the Website so that you may be aware of such change. Your continued use of the Website will then signify that you agree to such changes.  
Owing to the global nature of the internet, the information you provide may be transferred to companies outside the European Economic Area (EEA) that do not have similar protections in place to those which apply in the EEA regarding your data and its use as set out in this Policy. However, we have taken steps outlined in this Policy to protect the security of your information and will keep any transfers outside the EEA to a necessary minimum. By submitting your information you consent to these transfers.

What is our cookie policy

About Cookies  
When you visit our website, like most others, small pieces of data are sent to and retrieved from your browser, mostly in the form of ‘cookies’. These cookies can be used to store information about you or your device (computer, tablet or mobile) which can be used to present you with a more personalised web experience.

Analytics Cookies  
These cookies allow us to count page visits and traffic sources so we can measure and improve the performance of our site, using a service provided by Google Analytics.

Essential Cookies  
These cookies are necessary for the website to function and cannot be switched off in our systems. They are usually only set in response to actions made by you which amount to a request for services, such as logging in or filling in forms. You can set your browser to block or alert you about these cookies, but some parts of the site will not then work. These cookies do not store any personally identifiable information.

Functionality Cookies  
These cookies enable the website to provide value added services and functionality. They may be set by us or by third party content we have placed in our pages. If you do not allow these cookies then some or all of these services may not function properly.

Targeting Cookies  
These cookies may be set through our site by our advertising partners. They may be used by these companies to enable them to build a profile of your interests and show relevant adverts on other sites. They do not store any personally identifiable information, but are based on identifying your browser and internet device. If you do not allow these cookies, you will experience less targeted advertising.

How to Contact Us

We welcome your views about our Website and our Privacy Policy. If you would like to contact us with queries or comments please send an email to [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#592c323a2a1937382d30363738357438342c2a3c343c372d2a773a3634 "Customer Service") NATL Amusements (UK) Ltd: Redfield Way, Lenton, Nottingham, NG7 2UW Companies House 2141131
